[
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.4s-3.7s, 4.6s-9.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472827,
        "ecg_end": 475327
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-5.1s, 6.1s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472474,
        "ecg_end": 474974
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-3.1s, 4.1s-8.8s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472956,
        "ecg_end": 475456
    },
    {
        "question": "Assess this ECG and specify the location of the Premature ventricular contraction.Where does the Premature ventricular contraction appear in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.3s-3.6s, 4.6s-9.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472847,
        "ecg_end": 475347
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-3.3s, 4.3s-9.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472921,
        "ecg_end": 475421
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.8s, 3.8s-8.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473030,
        "ecg_end": 475530
    },
    {
        "question": "Please locate the specific location of the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-3.2s, 4.2s-8.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472949,
        "ecg_end": 475449
    },
    {
        "question": "Please locate the specific location of the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.8s-4.1s, 5.1s-9.8s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472721,
        "ecg_end": 475221
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.6s-4.8s, 5.8s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472530,
        "ecg_end": 475030
    },
    {
        "question": "Please locate the specific location of the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-3.1s, 4.0s-8.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 472978,
        "ecg_end": 475478
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell me where to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.7s-5.4s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473804,
        "ecg_end": 476304
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.7s, 1.7s-6.4s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473562,
        "ecg_end": 476062
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.1s-4.8s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473970,
        "ecg_end": 476470
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.6s, 1.6s-6.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473590,
        "ecg_end": 476090
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.2s-4.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473931,
        "ecg_end": 476431
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-4.2s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 474112,
        "ecg_end": 476612
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-4.4s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 474052,
        "ecg_end": 476552
    },
    {
        "question": "I need to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG; where should I look?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.2s-4.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473940,
        "ecg_end": 476440
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.9s-5.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 473753,
        "ecg_end": 476253
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you show me where the Premature ventricular contraction occurred on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-4.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 474048,
        "ecg_end": 476548
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Premature ventricular contraction located in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.6s-4.2s, 4.5s-7.4s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477395,
        "ecg_end": 479895
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 2.0s-4.6s, 4.9s-7.8s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477301,
        "ecg_end": 479801
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.6s-3.2s, 3.5s-6.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477641,
        "ecg_end": 480141
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.7s-3.3s, 3.5s-6.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477633,
        "ecg_end": 480133
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.8s, 4.1s-7.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477495,
        "ecg_end": 479995
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.1s-3.7s, 4.0s-6.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477527,
        "ecg_end": 480027
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.4s-4.0s, 4.3s-7.2s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477445,
        "ecg_end": 479945
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.2s-2.8s, 3.0s-6.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477758,
        "ecg_end": 480258
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.7s-4.3s, 4.5s-7.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477382,
        "ecg_end": 479882
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.5s, 2.8s-5.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 477820,
        "ecg_end": 480320
    },
    {
        "question": "Assess this ECG and specify the location of the Premature ventricular contraction.Where does the Premature ventricular contraction appear in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.3s, 1.6s-4.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478127,
        "ecg_end": 480627
    },
    {
        "question": "Assess this ECG and specify the location of the Premature ventricular contraction.Where does the Premature ventricular contraction appear in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.7s, 9.7s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478580,
        "ecg_end": 481080
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.2s, 1.5s-4.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478143,
        "ecg_end": 480643
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.4s, 0.6s-3.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478356,
        "ecg_end": 480856
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.9s, 1.2s-4.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478224,
        "ecg_end": 480724
    },
    {
        "question": "Assess this ECG and specify the location of the Premature ventricular contraction.Where does the Premature ventricular contraction appear in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.6s, 9.6s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478617,
        "ecg_end": 481117
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.2s-3.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478471,
        "ecg_end": 480971
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Premature ventricular contraction located in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.5s, 9.6s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478626,
        "ecg_end": 481126
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.4s, 0.7s-3.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478340,
        "ecg_end": 480840
    },
    {
        "question": "Assess this ECG and specify the location of the Premature ventricular contraction.Where does the Premature ventricular contraction appear in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-0.8s, 1.0s-4.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 478263,
        "ecg_end": 480763
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.3s, 9.9s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480702,
        "ecg_end": 483202
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.3s, 9.8s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480705,
        "ecg_end": 483205
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.9s-3.0s, 9.5s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480780,
        "ecg_end": 483280
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.7s-3.8s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480584,
        "ecg_end": 483084
    },
    {
        "question": "Please locate the specific location of the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-3.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480647,
        "ecg_end": 483147
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-3.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480553,
        "ecg_end": 483053
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Premature ventricular contraction located in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.9s, 8.4s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 481067,
        "ecg_end": 483567
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.9s, 8.5s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 481051,
        "ecg_end": 483551
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.0s, 8.5s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 481048,
        "ecg_end": 483548
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.1s-3.2s, 9.7s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 480734,
        "ecg_end": 483234
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.3s-2.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 483095,
        "ecg_end": 485595
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.9s-2.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482947,
        "ecg_end": 485447
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 483170,
        "ecg_end": 485670
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.7s-3.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482750,
        "ecg_end": 485250
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-3.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482784,
        "ecg_end": 485284
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 483267,
        "ecg_end": 485767
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482860,
        "ecg_end": 485360
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.9s-4.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482682,
        "ecg_end": 485182
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-3.6s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 482785,
        "ecg_end": 485285
    },
    {
        "question": "Check this ECG and tell me where the Premature ventricular contraction appears.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.5s-2.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 483046,
        "ecg_end": 485546
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.6s-3.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487246,
        "ecg_end": 489746
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell me where to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.7s-4.2s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 486969,
        "ecg_end": 489469
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me find where the Premature ventricular contraction shows up on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.4s-3.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487055,
        "ecg_end": 489555
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-4.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 486952,
        "ecg_end": 489452
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487453,
        "ecg_end": 489953
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell me where to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.9s-4.4s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 486933,
        "ecg_end": 489433
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487099,
        "ecg_end": 489599
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Premature ventricular contraction located in this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-4.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487028,
        "ecg_end": 489528
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.6s-4.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 486999,
        "ecg_end": 489499
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-4.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 487024,
        "ecg_end": 489524
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you show me where the Premature ventricular contraction occurred on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-1.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 497128,
        "ecg_end": 499628
    },
    {
        "question": "Check this ECG and tell me where the Premature ventricular contraction appears.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.2s-3.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496707,
        "ecg_end": 499207
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should I look to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-3.3s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496634,
        "ecg_end": 499134
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.1s-2.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496723,
        "ecg_end": 499223
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.9s-3.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496531,
        "ecg_end": 499031
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell me where to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.3s-2.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496943,
        "ecg_end": 499443
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.9s-2.7s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496774,
        "ecg_end": 499274
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you identify where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.1s-2.9s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496734,
        "ecg_end": 499234
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.8s-2.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496816,
        "ecg_end": 499316
    },
    {
        "question": "Check this ECG and tell me where the Premature ventricular contraction appears.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.2s-2.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 496954,
        "ecg_end": 499454
    },
    {
        "question": "I need to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG; where should I look?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-4.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 501747,
        "ecg_end": 504247
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.1s-2.8s, 9.1s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 502163,
        "ecg_end": 504663
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell me where to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.3s, 8.6s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 502295,
        "ecg_end": 504795
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.4s-3.2s, 9.5s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 502085,
        "ecg_end": 504585
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.9s-3.7s, 10.0s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 501951,
        "ecg_end": 504451
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is located on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.1s-2.8s, 9.1s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 502166,
        "ecg_end": 504666
    },
    {
        "question": "Determine where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this electrocardiogram.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.3s-4.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 501858,
        "ecg_end": 504358
    },
    {
        "question": "Check this ECG and tell me where the Premature ventricular contraction appears.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-4.5s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 501744,
        "ecg_end": 504244
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.3s-4.1s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 501850,
        "ecg_end": 504350
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.6s, 8.9s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 502227,
        "ecg_end": 504727
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.5s-4.3s, 9.1s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504068,
        "ecg_end": 506568
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you show me where the Premature ventricular contraction occurred on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.3s-4.0s, 8.9s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504127,
        "ecg_end": 506627
    },
    {
        "question": "Locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG for me, please.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.1s-2.8s, 7.7s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504430,
        "ecg_end": 506930
    },
    {
        "question": "I need to find the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG; where should I look?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.0s-2.4s, 7.3s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504530,
        "ecg_end": 507030
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.7s-3.5s, 8.3s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504266,
        "ecg_end": 506766
    },
    {
        "question": "Examine this ECG and point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is located.",
        "answer": "Duration: 0.4s-3.2s, 8.0s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504345,
        "ecg_end": 506845
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.4s-4.1s, 9.0s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504105,
        "ecg_end": 506605
    },
    {
        "question": "Could you point out where the Premature ventricular contraction is on this ECG?",
        "answer": "Duration: 2.0s-4.7s, 9.6s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 503960,
        "ecg_end": 506460
    },
    {
        "question": "On this ECG, where can I see the Premature ventricular contraction?",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.7s-4.4s, 9.3s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 504028,
        "ecg_end": 506528
    },
    {
        "question": "Help me locate the Premature ventricular contraction on this ECG.",
        "answer": "Duration: 1.8s-4.6s, 9.4s-10.0s",
        "ecg_path": [
            "e0103"
        ],
        "dataset": "european_st_t",
        "task": "location",
        "abnormal_type": "V",
        "ecg_start": 503994,
        "ecg_end": 506494
    }
]